<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>NUS GreyHats</title>
		<description>NUS GreyHats is a newly formed special interest group designed to spark students&#39; interest in information security and advance the level of security proficiency towards the aim of contributing to the growing need for cyber defenders in the government and private sectors.</description>
		<link>http://www.nusgreyhats.org/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://www.nusgreyhats.org//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>TrendMicroCTF - 500 Captchas! (Misc 300)</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;h1&gt;Welcome to Captcha Challenge!&lt;/h1&gt;
  The challenge description was a website, upon entering the website, you are allowed to register/sign in.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.nusgreyhats.org//TrendMicroCTF---500-Captchas!-(Misc-300)/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nusgreyhats.org//TrendMicroCTF---500-Captchas!-(Misc-300)/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Capture The Flag 101 Workshop</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/write-ups/img/thectf.jpg&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
NUS Greyhats Capture The Flag 101 is a capture-the-flag (CTF) style workshop that will be spanned over two Saturdays. Participants will learn techniques and tools to exploit software vulnerabilities to uncover secret flags hidden in various challenge. This workshop is designed to be progressive and is beginner friendly. In addition, we will have a live CTF scoreboard to show your ranking :)  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
You can sign up for the event &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1ppvnaRWzhwuSZ60CIKem4E37eyLQMbfltEw_xmutMBU/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; (while stocks last).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Date:&lt;/b&gt; 15 and 22 August 2015&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Time:&lt;/b&gt; 1PM - 5PM&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Venue:&lt;/b&gt; School of Computing COM 1 Seminar Room 3 &lt;br /&gt;
(Registration from 12.30PM onwards)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;b&gt;15 August 2015&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This session will focus on systems security which includes topics in source code auditing, representation of code as data, exploitation of insecure scripts, exploitation of format string bugs, and exploitation of memory corruption bugs.
&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.nusgreyhats.org//Capture-The-Flag-101-Workshop/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nusgreyhats.org//Capture-The-Flag-101-Workshop/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>POLICTF 2015 Write Up - John the Traveller (Web)</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;div class=&quot;holder&quot;&gt;   
				&lt;p&gt;
					Holidays are here! But John still hasn&#39;t decided where to spend them and time is running out: flights are overbooked and prices are rising every second. Fortunately, John just discovered a website where he can book last second flight to all the European capitals; however, there&#39;s no time to waste, so he just grabs his suitcase and thanks to his new smartphone he looks the city of his choice up while rushing to the airport. There he goes! Flight is booked so... hauskaa lomaa! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;a href=&quot;http://traveller.polictf.it/&quot;&gt;http://traveller.polictf.it/&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;hr /&gt;
	
				&lt;p&gt;
					We visited the site and saw the following page. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/write-ups/img/travellersite.JPG&quot; width=&quot;50%&quot; height=&quot;50%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;
				We tried to key into some arbitrary city, however, it returns back the same page. Looking back at the challenge description, we noticed something that stands out - &lt;b&gt;hauskaa lomaa&lt;/b&gt;. A search revealed that these two words is actually Finnish. We also found out that the capital of Finland is &lt;b&gt;Helsinki&lt;/b&gt;. Entering that into the search field and we got ....
					&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/write-ups/img/helsinki.JPG&quot; width=&quot;75%&quot; height=&quot;75%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				
				&lt;br /&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;
					Great. So the next step is to try and book the ticket. But how do we do so? The price is in px. Does it mean pixels?  The challenge also mentioned &quot;he just grabs his suitcase and thanks to his new smartphone&quot;. Let&#39;s try to adjust our browser size to one of the pixel size using Chrome browser dev tools. 
					&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/write-ups/img/devtools.JPG&quot; width=&quot;25%&quot; height=&quot;25%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
				<link>http://www.nusgreyhats.org//polictf-2015-write-up-john-the-traveller-(web)/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.nusgreyhats.org//polictf-2015-write-up-john-the-traveller-(web)/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
